[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "And I knew then I had a deal because Howard, the Buffett handshake means a lot, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Well, what I've learned growing up in our family is that, you know, integrity is everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard", "Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "How many men in the world or women, people you do business with, do you trust personally for big a deal on the strength of a handshake, percentage- wise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "We -- Well, I don't -- it's not the higher percentage but of the ones I've made deals with, I've decided that their handshake is good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Regardless of any bit of paper?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Regardless of any piece of paper.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "And do you still prefer to do business with a handshake?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Yeah, I prefer to do business with people I like.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "But let me ask you, HWB, what is the single best lesson you have learned from the elder Buffetts in your life, so far would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "Well both my grandfather and my father have been the most amazing role models that anyone could imagine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "RP", "CC", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "So we've got plenty of tweets pouring in Jane Fagan Smith (ph) said what's the most important advice you've ever had about investing that you would impart to others?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "VBD", "WP", "POS", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "Well, it's to look at stocks as part of the business rather than little things that bob up and down.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jane Fagan Smith"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 63, "question": "Do you have to personally enjoy the stocks that you buy big in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 64, "answer": "Well, I enjoyed them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "So we used a major rock star writers, there was one request, anything Coca-Cola related?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NN", ",", "NN", "-NONE-", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Coca-Cola"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "I'm a BlackBerry relic, I still hang on to the BlackBerry, it turns that HWB here has two BlackBerries?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "How long have you had that one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, I don't throw anything away until I got it 20 or 25 years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "Do you use e-mail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "I do it through my assistant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Microsoft"], "LOCATION": ["Minneapolis"], "PERSON": ["Jeff Wright"]}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Who to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "I sent it to Jeff Wright at Microsoft and it ended up in court in Minneapolis court.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, it's not so old.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "You're not into flashy things, are you really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Well, I have everything I want, you know, I'm happy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", ":", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "... the rent went down?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Yeah, and I started feeding candy and pie and all this ....", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "So it didn't work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "No, not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "... so that there was no wavering on your part?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "It was a deal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "It seems to me that the two incentives, one worked and one didn't would you regret the weight incentive that you laid down with your son?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CD", "VBD", "CC", "CD", "VBD", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "I would say it was dumb.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "Has he had the same criteria?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "You know, I don't think I've ever done that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "All three of your children went to public schools?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "That's true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "CD", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 155, "question": "You don't seem to faze, why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Well, for one thing, if they combine their credits, we can get one degree and that's...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Was he -- I don't want to use the word mean, but was he a little tight fisted, Howard, from the way you're painting this picture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "No, you painted it that way.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "But, you would only hear one side of the call?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Yes, but he can figure out how those go on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$34 billion"]}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 191, "question": "And how much did you pay?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 192, "answer": "$34 billion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "Do you often make big mistakes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$400 million"], "PERSON": ["Dexter Shoe"]}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CD", "POS", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "$", "CD", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "What's been the one you think I should never have done that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "ARREN BUFFETT: Well, I bought a company in the mid 90's called Dexter Shoe and paid $400 million for it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 213, "question": "Would you agree with that, Warren?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 214, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "JJR", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Tell me why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Well, she is -- first of all, she did something, you had my dad saying earlier which is, she provided unconditional love to all three of us.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "EX", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "But not you Howard, what did you do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "Well, I had a roll of windows in my room and, you know, I opened the window up, we had this greenhouse so I'd be careful climbing out because I don't want to go through the glass, but I got down and we had our charge account at the local hardware store about five blocks away and I went up there and I convinced the guy to let me charge a hasp lock, I had to buy a screw driver because I didn't have any tools and I get everything I needed and I crawled back up in and I locked her out.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Howard"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "How did you mother react?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "I think as it is, she probably got a kick out of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "How did you change?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "I slowly grew up and I wouldn't have otherwise.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Just to override, anything else you would write?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "Sure, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "I mean tell me about what is like growing up in this kind of family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, to be frank it's been normal in a sense that we grew up in a normal house.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", ":", "WP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Warren, what other the key values that you would like to see other people recognize in your children, your grandchildren, your family, your extended family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Well, I want them to be good citizens, good parents that the -- what the world would be better off because they were here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "What is your definition of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Well, I'm not sure I can give you a great one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "He says its thread bare and dust and has cobwebs, right Howard?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "VBZ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I'm not sure where the time lock is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Howard tell me about this book \"Forty Chances\", why the title?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, the \"Forty Chances\" comes from actually my career farming.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Well, one of the biggest things I've learned is -- I mean there's a lot of great organizations out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gage"]}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "What do you make of what he's achieved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, he's offered in the premise as my other two children and that it's a (Gage) foundation so that all lives have equal value.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "Proud of him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "I'm very proud of him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "Can you do any better on salary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "Unfortunately, that range is at a corporate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$0.25"]}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "$", "CD", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "What about mileage when I use my car, I mean gas ain't cheap, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "We think the $0.25 a mile is pretty generous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Warren Buffett negotiating with the gang on NBC's The Office that legendary attention to details, I'm met his family, one of the most influential in the world back now with the three generations of Buffetts, Warren, Howard G, and Howard W. Do you enjoy being an actor there, Warren, well you're quite good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "EX", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "I wouldn't say that, but nice thing about being mildly famous is that the worst you are the better people like it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NBC"], "LOCATION": ["Warren"], "PERSON": ["Howard G", "Howard W.", "Warren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "``", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 413, "question": "What is do you think most people when they see you in the street recognize you, ask you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJS", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "Oh, they come up with, you know, they say, \"Are you really?\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 417, "question": "If I was to ask you that now, what would the answers be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "DT", "NNS", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 418, "answer": "Well, let's take a look.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Is this Edward (inaudible) on television before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "I got this wallet for -- here's my.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Edward"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "How long have you had it first?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "Probably about 20 years, maybe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1964"]}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "And what do you have in it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "Here's my American express card from 1964.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "That's the one you've had the whole time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Yes, well it goes with my cell phone.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "What other cards do you have?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "Well, I have a variety of cards, but there's a picture of the family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "IN", "JJ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 439, "question": "And how much cash?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "More than usual that ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Of all the places you've been, of all the issues you've dealt with, what is being the most powerful to you personally?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "The resiliency of people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "Seems like (inaudible) on air in CNN in three years there's going to be some crisis involving Washington, debt ceilings, shutdowns, how do we try and bring an end to all this and actually move forward for the benefit of the American economy and the American people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "NN", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "CC", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "I think that both parties should declare the debt limit as a political weapon of mass destruction which can't be use.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "What is the future for America Incorporated do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Terrific, terrific.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Well you an multiply all the value but it's all going to plan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank Sinatra"]}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Have you ever met Frank Sinatra before he died?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "No I never met Frank Sinatra.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Frank Sinatra"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "You're a fan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I'm a fan.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "ORGAN: And you're a fan of the Ukulele?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "Yes and you just (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "A bit inundated with tweets, many of them say, these Buffett boys are a lot of fun aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "We had a lot of fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "You don't do this kind of interview very often Warren, how do you enjoy the last hour?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "I've enjoyed it a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "A teacher, teacher, yeah, well actually I'd like to remembered as the oldest man that ever lived, I'm sure that's with the (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "Which moment would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "The time with my dad, some moment, any moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "William Shatner how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "Electric.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William Shatner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Come on, how old are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "82.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "What is the secret to eternal youth, William Shatner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Well first of all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["William Shatner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 568, "question": "Why have you never become an American citizen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 569, "answer": "All those lines I had to learn to, I swear allegiance, then I had to memorize that stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Well what would you make of the whole, never mind all the debt standoff, what do you make of the ObamaCare dispute?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "We don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "CC", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 580, "question": "How would Captain James T. Kirk run America right now if he was President?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 581, "answer": "Fire them all and have a new election.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James T. Kirk"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "... it has to be mysterious and weird and strange?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Well it's not weird and strange.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What's the simple answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "We are composed of all of it and we have to maintain control of those impulses that are negative.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Do you ever get highly emotional?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "All the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "About the album?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", ":", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "Do you know where you're going?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "No, the best journeys -- are when you don't know where you're going and you make the discovery as you go along from point to point.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Billy Sherwood"]}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "CC", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "When you're making this music?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Well I felt transported by writing the lyrics and then when Billy Sherwood wove the music around my words and then we have these great musicians come in and play (inaudible).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Do you see people walking around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "Yes, there a number of residents that are walking around.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Have you ever seen anything like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "This -- it does look quite similar to disasters I have seen in the past just the sheer devastation and the debris everywhere.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 681, "question": "Paula, any indication -- are you getting any numbers on the death toll?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 682, "answer": "At this point, we're not getting any numbers at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]